I'm a big fan of science I follow it
religiously and the famous science Minh
Charles Darwin once told me that humans
and all creatures we have the same
biological drive it's to survive and
then propagate the species and if you've
ever been to an airport or tried to park
at a Trader Joe's you've probably
noticed there are a lot of us we are one
of the successful list
propagation the earth so much so now
that we're choking the planet which we
need to live we're not done with the
least yet and I don't think we're gonna
get our deposit back because global
warming is out of control but I have a
great idea on how to fix it everybody
needs to run their air conditioner all
the time with their windows open
[Applause]
it's a no-brainer which is how I thought
of it
when you're hot you turn on the air when
the planets hot deutsches turn on the
air what could be obvious er than that I
got the idea when I saw a cat go from
the Sun to the shade yeah when hot and
cold you'll be less hot I don't know
what part of that flowchart is tripping
all you guys up but even mr. pickle's
has it figured out all right it's it's
not rocket surgery okay it's a button
it's you know what's great about our
leaders in Washington me either it's all
talk and no action it's not that
greenhouse gases I'm worried about it's
those White House gas bags because all
their hot air is only making the globe
even warmer so now we got a big problem
and a whole bunch of complainers but
only one thinker boy I'm a problem
thinker I've got a problem thinking
right now it's called Operation chill
off which is what everyone needs to do
just chill off that's what my mom packed
oh he says to me because sometimes it
gets too hot in the basement for me to
sleep but I didn't come here tonight to
talk about Pat because she's not the
boss of me right now
I came here to share great ideas on how
to lower temperatures around the world
here's one convert to the metric system
when we convert to the metric system
temperatures will drop 50 degrees
overnight that's a scientific fact
[Applause]
severe drop 50 degrees incident global
Colden
well the other metric system in
Scandinavia it's not hot there is that
magic no it's metric and I know the
difference I love magic ever since I was
a little kid and my dad disappeared
abracadabra
but I didn't come here tonight to talk
about Rick all right and I know what
you're thinking sir you're thinking I
don't want to convert to the metric
system because then we'll have a bunch
of metric ins come into our lab well
then you're a measure Asst and you need
to chill off because once you go metric
you won't go back am i right ladies what
are you gonna do to stop them build a
wall along 1,100 kilometers wide and
like nine gallons tall well who-who do
you thinks gonna measure that while you
are with your yardstick no way hose f a
metric it is but you're totally
digressing the subject mr. interrupter
the problem isn't metric ins it's global
warming and we need to save the planet
so we can have a place to live hola
and I have a great idea for that all
right if you if you see someone who
doesn't recycle or they keep the water
on while they're brushing their teeth or
they leave all the lights on their house
when they leave if you see someone who
does that just don't mate with them and
that way we can breed those traits out
of the gene pool
[Applause]
don't mates don't dates don't fornicate
don't propagate don't Kapolei
don't even cop a feel alright because
then those jack butts are killing the
planet mostly with with plastic yeah
did you know 40% of all plastic is used
only once and then it's gone waste
yeah that's it's like a liberal arts
degree or something that's
[Applause]
you
hey did you know that Drybar comedy has
their own app you can download it now to
watch save and share clips or watch my
whole special you're welcome